STANDARD FOR LIFE
Here is the prayer line section of the SCOAN, where God's Spirit is the force behind His Word.
God's service is more than mere preaching or teaching but it is of power.
As wise man Christopher moves with the force of God, he sees the manifestation of the evil spirit
in the life of this lady.
Watch how the evil spirit, which made her to be winding around is conquered in Jesus' name.
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
All over your body, Holy Ghost fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
You demon.
Fire, in the name of Jesus!
Who are you?
Why are you asking me again?
I told you before.
I'm the curse of the family.
That is number one.
Who is number two?
The idol.
Who is number three?
A snake.
Who is number four?
Her husband.
As a snake, what have you done to this lady?
I destroyed her career.
What have you done to the family members?
I have no business with the family.
Why do you choose to destroy her?
She is supposed to be a nurse.
For what?
That was why I cancelled her results.
She can't read.
Whenever she wants to read I would just go on her head and sit down.
When you sit on her head what will happen?
She can't read.
If she reads she'll forget.
She will be lazy. She will complain that she can't read.
As an idol, what have you done to her?
They are supposed to serve me.
What have you done to them?
I caused them bad luck.
What is happening to them?
To their careers and marriages?
Marriage? They are moving in circles.
Who is the cause?
The idol from the father's side and from the mother's side.
Open your eyes.
Look at these people.
Look at the first lady.
Look at her.
Who is she to you?
They are parts of the bad luck.
Speak louder.
Look at the next lady.
Who is she to you?
This one is a curse to the family.
We sent her to come and destroy the family.
Who, which one?
This one.
She is an agent.
We sent her to destroy the family.
We turned her in the womb; the idol of the family.
Who is she to you?
She is my younger sister.
She is my older sister.
Did you hear that?
They are all bad luck; they won't get married.
Bride price – no.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Ask her; the other sister, she's somewhere.
We don't know.
We just sent her out of the house.
She has two kids but no bride price.
Yes, it's true.
What can you say about her?
My older sister is a doctor by profession and she has two children by a guy and he did not pay the dowry.
Nothing.
She fights with the mum.
She will call the mum witch.
Yes.
Who is the cause?
The curse.
This is my older sister.
This is the one who got married.
She has two kids but no bride price.
Is she the one you are talking about?
Which one?
This one has two kids?
She has two kids but no bride price.
This one got married five months ago and she came back.
Yes, the curse.
I was sent on an errand; I don't know.
I was just asked to follow her.
How did you enter this lady?
Right from when she was born.
What she is saying is true.
We school in Delta State University.
Both of us are in the same hostel.
Each time I tell her about suitors that come to me, before you know it, they will just run away.
Anything you tell her, the thing will not come to pass.
She is very secretive and does not tell anyone anything about herself.
I want to go.
What is in this place that is against you demons?
Fire.
How many demonic powers do you have in this body?
I told you before, just four.
Right now, your mission has come to an end.
This is the temple of the Holy Spirit.
Get out.
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ.
Now, move like a snake.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Come back here.
Move like a snake.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Now, get out.
Come out of her, you demon!
Out!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Fire!
Remove the rings.
Remove them!
What are you removing?
Rings.
Speak louder - what are you removing?
From your head to your toe - everything that belongs to you - remove it.
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
In Jesus' name!
Amen.
You are delivered.
Thank You, Jesus.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
How are you?
I am fine.
Can you remember what you said?
Not really; I know I said something but I can't recall.
You said that you were a snake with another four demons in your body.
No.
This is your sister?
Yes, my older sister.
This is your younger sister?
My younger one next to me; yes.
Her past is over; so, glory be to God, she's completely delivered.
She's a new creation.
Old things pass away.
Nobody should use what she had said against her.
That demonic being that spoke was cast out by Jesus and now, she is free.
If you say what she has said or use it against her, you will be tempted.
We pray that you will not be tempted, in Jesus' name.
Thank You, Jesus! I'm free!
Thank You, Jesus! My sister is free!
Thank You, Jesus!
You are free.
Thank You, Jesus! I'm free!
All over your body – fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Stand up!
Who are you?
I am from the water.
What is your mission?
To monitor the family.
What have you done to the family so far?
No marriage; suitors come and go.
No good luck; quarrel everywhere.
What have you done to this lady?
She's very bright.
I have destroyed her.
No good people come her way.
She travels a lot.
She followed friends.
How did you enter her body?
When she was born.
Her mother threw away her placenta in the river.
What is your business with the placenta?
This is what we use against her.
Ever since you used it what has been happening to her?
She's rude, she's stubborn, she doesn’t hear.
Anything you tell her; nothing.
All what she wants is to do what she wants to do.
Who made her to be so?
Me.
Why?
Because I love her.
This is not a place you can live.
This is the temple of the Spirit of God.
Open you eyes!
Look at these people.
Who are they to you?
I don’t know them.
Look at this one.
I don’t know her.
I don’t know.
You are welcome.
Thank you, sir.
She is my younger sister.
She is very stubborn.
She doesn’t even go to school.
She is very "insultive", aggressive; she doesn’t have respect for anybody, even towards my mum and dad.
She fights with my mum.
She goes to clubs and follows friends.
She goes to clubs every day from Monday to Sunday.
She doesn’t stay at home.
All of her body is full with tattoos.
She has them on her waist, her breast – all over her body are tattoos.
What can you say about her?
Everything my sister said.
Most of the injuries on my body - she gave them to me.
Most of the injuries you have, she gave them to you?
Whenever she's angry she'll bring bottles or knives, anything in her hand.
She may even break the table in the sitting room.
Who made her to possess this kind of attitude?
From the water.
Since you are a stranger, get out.
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
All over your body, Holy Ghost Fire!
Come out of this body, you demon.
Now go.
Thank You, Lord.
In Jesus' name, Amen.
Stand up.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
How are you?
I am fine.
Open your eyes and look at these people.
Who is this lady to you?
My older sister.
This is your sister and this is your sister.
Can you see?
Her past is over.
Do not use what she has confessed in the past against her.
Otherwise, everybody here will be tempted.
She is free; you too are free.
In Jesus' name.
Thank You, Jesus! We are delivered!
Thank You, Jesus!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God with us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Sophia.
I am 21 years old and I am from Delta, Nigeria.
The lady standing beside me is my sister.
The problem that brought me to the SCOAN started when I was growing up, at the tender age of six;
I started seeing a man coming to make love to me in my dreams.
I would see myself as a fish in the water and eating with people in my dreams.
As I was growing up, the problem became worse.
I would see myself as a princess, doing my hair in the water in my dreams.
When I was in secondary school, I wanted to write an exam but my parents couldn't afford it.
I decided to go into a relationship.
When I would go into relationships, they wouldn't work out.
The man would say that I appeared to them as a snake and chased them or fight with them
as a mermaid in their dreams.
As a result, I started going to churches, looking for deliverance.
I went to several churches.
I went to a spiritualist and I was told I suffered from a spiritual husband and that I should go
and serve the spiritual husband.
The spiritualist told me to do a concoction.
After he did the concoction for me, the same night, the spiritual husband came again.
He came back with two men; it was worse.
From there, I went to different places and started meeting different spiritualists.
One spiritualist called me and told me that most girls don't make it just like that,
that they used to give them something, in order to make it.
The spiritualist called me inside his office and said he was going to give me something to wear on my eyes,
to rub on my lips and all over my body; he said that anything I would tell a man, he would do it for me.
The spiritualist gave it to me; I rubbed it on my lips, eyes and all over my body.
As soon as I walked past any man in that area, he would want to go out with me.
That was how I was doing it.
It came to a time where it became worse.
I started going to the clubs, moving with different people because the urge I had for men was much.
I had an encounter with someone and I was arrested; I slept in the prison cell for three days.
The first night, something entered me.
I was so strong; I could talk to the policeman any way I liked and I would fight with them.
Ever since I left the police station, it became worse.
I started stealing.
How would you go about using these charms that the spiritualist gave you to attract men
and in the same way also steal from them?
The one in my eyes, whenever I used it, I would look directly into their eyes,
blink my eyes and push out my lips.
The next thing was that they would say I had sexy eyes.
That meant they had already fallen for the charm.
We would go to the hotel and after the encounter,
I would deceive them and tell them to go downstairs to get something.
The spirit would tell me where the money was; when I would look at the room, I would know the place.
I would collect their money, their phones and leave.
I would dress very well so nobody would ask me any questions.
That was what I would normally do.
The men that invite you to meet them in the hotel - after meeting them, as they are not there,
you would now steal their money and you would know where the money was kept?
That spirit would tell you where the money were kept?
Yes.
Even some of them, I would lock them in the bathroom, increase the volume on the television and leave.
That was what I was doing.
We understand what our sister is saying.
After meeting with the man she would lock him in the bathroom, then increase the volume of the television
and then steal his money.
What were you using such money for?
I would use the money to buy clothes and things.
I would keep the money somewhere and would go to collect it but the money would vanish.
Even when I'd lay out my clothes, the next morning, I would not find them there.
During this period, that was how you were getting money; by meeting these men,
stealing from them and sleeping with them.
Is that right?
Yes, that was it.
Can you just explain more about how this problem really affected not only yourself but the whole family?
The evil spirit affected my family so much.
Sometimes after stealing, people would know that I had stolen from them
and would then come to my house to tell my family what I had done.
I would deny it.
I was very quiet in my house, so my mum would always fight for me that I hadn't done anything.
Even your parents did not know what you were doing?
Yes, because I was very quiet in the house.
Tell us what was your behavior in the house when you were with your parents
compared to you behavior outside.
When I was in my house, I would be very quiet, obedient and very good
but whenever I was outside, the evil spirit would enter me and I’d misbehave.
You said that you were going to clubs.
What would you do, when you were in clubs, to attract men that you would be able to sleep with them?
When I'd go to the clubs, I'd put the charm on my lips, eyes and all over my body.
Any man that would walk past would say he wanted to go out with me.
We would then discuss how much he would pay me for the night.
That was what I was doing.
The evil spirit affected me badly.
The spirit of stealing was so terrible because I would be tempted.
After spending 20 000 naira, I would steal something that cost 50 naira.
It was very bad.
Sometime last year, my senior sister came to the SCOAN.
In my house, we couldn’t get married; that was the problem everyone was facing in the family.
My senior sister came to the SCOAN and received the Anointing Water.
When I got home, my mum said I should minister the Anointing Water.
I ministered the Anointing Water and I manifested.
Then I came to The SCOAN for my deliverance.
Let's put our hands for Jesus Christ!
When I came to the SCOAN, I was sitting far towards the back but when the wise man Christopher was close,
I started running away.
They brought me back twice and he prayed for me.
The spirit that was inside of me left.
Glory by to God Almighty.
Tell us - ever since your deliverance - what is your testimony now?
What changes you have seen in your life?
I have seen a lot of changes.
Before when the spirit would enter me, I'd take my things and leave the house.
When I slept, I saw three snakes leaving my body.
I know I am delivered; I am calm.
You mean that after your deliverance you had a dream - what happened in that dream?
I saw three snakes – two big ones, a green one and a tiny one.
They all came out of my body – I killed two and chased the other one.
It went inside the bush.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
That is the confirmation of the deliverance she received.
Sister, you said before that you were stealing, lying, meeting men and using the powers that you obtained
from the witch doctor to seduce and attract men.
Ever since your deliverance, what can you say now about those areas?
Do you still have that spirit pushing you to steal, lie, meet with men?
No. I am free.
Glory be to God Almighty.
We thank Jesus Christ for your life.
I think you are in a wonderful position to advise young people around the world.
You are a young lady, you are only 21 years old.
With your experiences in life; all the time before - with those evil spirits, and now when you are delivered,
what do you want to advise young people around the world watching you right now on Emmanuel TV?
My advice is to tell people that there is nothing in the world.
Everything belongs to God, so they should come to God, pray to God because He answers prayers.
Definitely, He will answer them.
It is just a matter of being patient.
How did this affect your education, when you were living this kind of a life-style?
It affected my education badly.
I wrote an exam four years ago and when I went to collect the results,
I was told that the results were
As a result, I could not gain admission.
I was doing a programme and I was sleeping with men to pay my school fees.
But still, I could not study in school, I hated school and couldn’t go any longer.
Even the courses I paid for, I would pay people to write them and then, I paid the lecturer,
but I would still have a carry-over.
That was the problem I was facing in school.
Right now, we want to hear from your sister as well, who was also privileged to receive a mighty deliverance,
alongside you, the day she came.
Sister, you're welcome.
Tell us your name, and where you are from.
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Faith, I am from Delta State, Nigeria.
I am 18 years old.
The problems that brought me to the SCOAN were a family curse and a spiritual husband.
When I was small, I was stubborn; anything you would tell me to do, I wouldn't do it.
Whatever was in my mind, that was what I would do.
I would fight.
My friends couldn’t fight because if they did, I'd do something crazy to them before I would get myself.
There was a day I woke up and left to see a friend.
That day, my friend started introducing me to men.
She said I should come with her, that in my house there was no money, and that we were suffering;
I should come and sleep with men, so I'd have money to take care of myself.
How old were you when you started this?
I was 14 years old.
She started introducing me to men and I would sleep with them for money.
The men would give me money.
As time went on, she would take me to different men; sometimes, we would go out to the clubs.
When we'd get to the clubs, men would ask me how much for the night.
I'd tell them to bring a certain amount of money and I'd go with them.
As time went on, my friend said that we weren't making good money, that we should go to a spiritualist,
so they could help us get more money.
She took me to a spiritualist and he gave me something to use.
He said that the spiritual husband was causing me to have bad luck.
He gave me a charm that anywhere I'd go, men would give me anything I asked for.
He put the charm on my forehead and on my lips.
Whenever I went anywhere, if we were 10 in number, I would be the first person a man would talk to.
He would tell me that I was beautiful and ask for my number.
From there, we were sleeping with men.
I travelled to different cities to meet men.
She introduced me to friends who said I had to join a cult before I could be friends with them.
I said I couldn’t do that but they told me that I had to or I had to stop going out with them.
I needed money and I liked clubbing.
Most times I slept with men, I would ask why I had done it but I wouldn't know I was doing it.
Afterwards, I'd get myself and I knew I had done something bad.
I would start crying.
My friend would ask me if I was crazy, why was I crying, that I was crying like a baby;
she said she would push me out.
I would find the strength to stay with them.
You said that your friends had told you to join a cult.
Is that right?
Yes.
What happened during this initiation?
For the initiation, there was a procedure.
The man would sleep with you and afterwards, they would beat you.
Then, you are initiated.
Others had to pay money.
As for myself, I didn’t want any mark on my body, so I paid them the money.
They told me that anything I saw there, I could not say outside and they cut my hand
and I took an oath with my blood.
What did they ask you to do show that you are a part of that cult?
In the cult, the girls were tough.
They drew a tattoo on my arm with the name they gave me.
They told you that you should put this tattoo to show that you are a part of that cult?
Yes.
How old were you when you joined this cult?
I was 16 years old.
16 years old.
Do you mean to say that there are other tattoos on your body as well?
Yes. The other tattoo is of a dollar sign.
If I wanted, I could get any tattoo I liked, so I got this one of a dollar sign.
Your sister is saying that when she joined that cult she was told to wear a tattoo and they gave her the name
of Arsa, which was tattooed on her body.
They also said, "if you want any other tattoo, you can".
She chose to make a sign of a dollar, sign of money as a tattoo on her body.
Tell us, why did you choose this tattoo of a dollar sign?
Why did you choose to make a tattoo with money sign on your body?
When I was in the streets, no relationship would ever work out.
I decided that all I needed in life was money.
With money, you are OK.
So the dollar sign was for money.
You believed that as long as you could get money you'd be OK.
Everything about you was just to get money, meet men, sleep with them and get money.
Yes.
Tell us, what for you would be using such money.
Would you use it for anything profitable?
We would use the money to get drinks in the clubs, buy clothes and travel to the best places to enjoy ourselves.
You were never actually able to use the money for anything really profitable.
You would just use it for drinking, smoking, buying clothes and then the money would go.
Yes.
In the course of meeting men, what other things did you begin to do to such men
in order to obtain money from them?
There was a day I walked up to a man and I saw money on his table; the evil spirit in me to take the money.
Since the day I collected money from that man, I started collecting money from men.
There was no way they would drop money and I wouldn’t know it was there.
I would go there and take the money.
My friends would say that there was money missing.
They couldn’t believe that I was the one taking the money; I looked too innocent.
They would start accusing someone else.
After sleeping with a men, they would pay you and you would also steal money from them?
Yes.
And they never suspected that you were the one who stole the money.
Tell us, as you were continuing this kind of life-style...
You mean to say that you left your home at the age of 14?
Yes, I left home.
They were looking for me but I didn’t give them my address of where I was staying.
Right from the age of 14 you'd left your house and were moving around, sleeping with men to get money
and moving out with friends?
Yes.
Each time you go to the club - what do you do to attract men, that they would meet with you?
I know how to dance very well.
When I started dancing in the club, men would be fighting to be with me.
Tell us, did you also have any experiences in this course of prostitution that you would never forget?
Maybe you encountered a man that wanted to do something to you?
Like your sister said earlier - in terms of rituals?
What kind of encounters did you have during that period?
Yes, I had an encounter I will never forget.
There was a day three of my friends were called and told to come with girls and I was one of them.
We were in a vehicle and the next thing, I found myself in the forest.
We were all naked, wearing only our panties and bras.
They tied our hair and priced each of our heads at 500 000 naira.
I thought I was going to die that day and prayed that God should forgive my sin.
I was just praying.
When I got back, my mum said that same night she had a dream that they wanted to kill me;
she was even praying.
I just prayed.
The men were huge.
There were human heads, babies, school bags, uniforms; everything was there.
The girl that brought us in the vehicle told us that our heads were not good,
that we just caused them bad luck.
After 12 o'clock in the night, we were running through the forest; it was raining.
That was how we escaped.
The women at the market gave us clothes to cover ourselves as we travelled back.T
This is a kind of experience you had as a prostitute.
Have you ever had a similar encounter with a man in the hotel?
I had an encounter with a man who said he was a pastor.
He told me I looked beautiful, that I was nice and that I was going to do a job for him.
He said he was a pastor, that he had a programme where he would preach and see visions.
He introduced me to some girls who worked with him.
He would tell me what to do.
We would go to the church and the girls would take me close to men who had money.
I would talk to the man, collect his phone number and name.
I would tell them about the man.
The 'pastor' would go to the programme and ask of that man.
He would tell him to come out and tell his phone number.
He would make a huge amount of money from the man.
That was the plan that that man who claimed to be a pastor had with you, that you would come to the church
befriend someone there, collect their details, give them to that man, and then in public he would supposedly
prophesy about it in order to get money from that man.
Yes.
In the process of doing that work for him, he travelled out of the country.
When he came back, I told him I wasn't around; he said he'd find someone else.
Have you ever tried to stop this kind of life-style before your coming to the Synagogue?
Yes, I tried to stop but there was no way.
When I would stop, I would bring my things back to the house but things were not OK.
There was no money.
The evil spirit would be asking me what I was still doing there, that I was hungry and had nothing to wear;
I would go back to the streets.
OK, we can really understand from our sister what has been happening in her life.
This is what she has passed through.
We thank God Almighty that you are here today with your sister as a testimony to the glory of God.
Tell us, what happened when you came here to the SCOAN with your sister.
Last year in November, my senior sister came to the SCOAN she received the Anointing Water
and brought it home.
She said that everybody should minister the Anointing Water to themselves.
When I ministered the Anointing Water to myself, I was dizzy and stood up.
My friends would come and call me to go out but I would tell them I didn't want to go.
Most times when I would dream, I would see pastors telling me that this wasn't the way for me to enjoy life.
I decided to come to the SCOAN.
When coming to the SCOAN every way was blocked; since December, we were planning on coming here
but there was no money.
I couldn’t go anywhere; there was no money.
After December, the New Year period, I said we must come to the SCOAN.
At the prayer line, my sister was delivered.
When the wise man moved closer to me, there was fire all over him; I couldn't look at him.
I was not myself, until I stood up from the floor.
Tell us sister, ever since your deliverance - what is your testimony?
How is your live changed?
My life is OK.
I can see things and no longer have interest in taking them.
I am OK.
My friends would call and ask me where I was and I would tell them not to call my number anymore,
that I'm not into that.
My friends said that for me to change, she too would change, that she was going to come to the SCOAN
because the kind of life she was living she didn’t like it.
You mean your friends who were into the same life-style, because of the change in your life-style said that
they also want come to the SCOAN?
Yes.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ for that wonderful change.
What about spirit of lust, that pushed you to be sleeping with men?
How are you right now?
Do you still have that spirit pushing you?
No.
How have you been sleeping?
It has been two months since my deliverance and I no longer have interest in meeting men.
Glory be to God Almighty.
We thank Jesus Christ for your life and life of your sister.
I think you are in the position to really advise once again young people around the world.
What do you really want to advise young people who are watching you right now?
Young people who are poor, I want to tell them that if anybody that deceives them to come with them
to make money, the money you will make, there is nothing to gain from it; you cannot use it to do anything.
If they tell you to go to spiritualists, they are putting more problems into your life;
there is nothing they can do for you.
So, you are advising people to embrace Jesus Christ... ?
Yes.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of all Nations
Emmanuel TV – changing lives, changing nations and changing the world.
TT ROBERT BEGIER 22/06/2018